I'll open the door, get out of the way and clear this team. Hurry, hurry, someone is coming to the dark room. Flash, flash!
What are you doing? I'm taking medicine, can't you see how disabled I am? What medicine did you take? Give it a flash,
I just cleaned it out. I said, I can't wait any longer. This is an evil plan.
I've been practicing for a month and I'm still not good at it. I hit anyone I see. I can't even get out of space and I'm still spanking! My favorite,
Sorry mine. No, I don't blame you, it's me.
I'm a little bit too, I'm a little too impatient too, okay. But this issue of collaboration,
We really need to practice hard. We've been playing together for almost a month now, and it's all because of your problems that you can't keep up.
Finally lost. Man, I admit it, I’m just a good player, and I really can’t keep up with synergy.
Just find someone else to play with you. Well, how can cement and gas tanks be valuable enough? My bag is almost full.
Hey, Brother Hao, aren't you going to attack fiercely? Hey, I won’t tell you anymore, we got the treasure map.
You shoot an arrow in front, be careful if someone plots against you. Oh oh, OK, OK. Wow, hey,
There's someone here! Hey, be careful ahead, be careful! Hey, beautiful! Brother Hao,
Your map understanding is so awesome! Hey, brothers, brothers, let’s go treasure hunting at point eight! ah.
What treasure map? What the hell is this! This new event has just been launched today, Brother Hao, don’t you know?
Hey, that’s right. I see you’ve been practicing shooting and shooting every day for the past month. It’s both a top-secret space flight and a prison.
You can play Delta for more than ten hours a day. I think you are tired! But what do you mean by this prop?
Where are you going? This is a new activity, hey, let me tell you,
You can receive or pick up this treasure map through airdrops, and then mark the location on the map.
Then you look here to dig for Asara's treasure, it's very fun.
Then I suggest you don't go to No. 8. It's easy to meet people there, and it's difficult to get out once you get in.
Oh, you can go a little further to No. 4. It may not be easy to meet people on the road at this time.
Even if they meet, they may just be running for the knife, and there will be little pressure. OK, hey, brothers,
I have a great master here, and it is definitely right to follow his instructions. Hey, you follow me, you follow me. Wow,
Speak up, brothers! Wow! ha!
Hey, Brother Hao, actually I see that you are so tired every day recently and you are always quarreling with your teammates, then...
Have you ever thought about why you rush to make money? That's for sure. Hey, look,
In fact, you don't know exactly why, but you are really too strong, and sometimes you will be very tired.
Although Hammer and I are usually good at playing, we are very happy occasionally when we run into Dangdang Mouse.
I still remember you taking me on top secrets before.
I didn't know what to do when I went in, and it was always a drag.
Although it is true that you spent a lot of money on me, I really don’t have much gaming experience.
I actually still think this game was the most fun when I first played it. We beat a team and came out again,
I would be happy if I could eat hundreds of thousands. But now, you eat hundreds and tens of millions every day,
This thing cannot be turned into bank deposits. I play games every day and gain so much energy and coins. Hey,
I'll make some herbal tea from our hometown for you to drink.
That makes sense, bro. Oh, just play games and have fun. Hey, come and dig treasures with us!
If you are tired from space travel, come to our Tibetan Palace to relax. OK, let’s dig for treasure!